Regards, Youtube. I'm James, I'm a fan of
the data and I can't wait to show you how
you can turn him into an office superhero with Power
Bi.
This is the first in a series of videos aimed
at helping you make a tremendous impact on your business.
In this video we will talk about the most fundamental
elements of Barbie.
There are included
the steps of. Obtain data,
transform data and load the data.
And we will talk about the 3 views of paulie
once the data, report, data
and model are loaded, let's take a look at the
laptop.
Let's start with getting pavia and use the desktop app
to design the travel solution before publishing it to the
cloud, where it
is automatically updated to get it from the app store.
App Store. It will ensure that it updates automatically once
installed now via and click get data.
Today we will take out of an Excel workbook that
I made
with 3 sheets, now that we got the 3 sheets
we can let Pavia e do its magic and make
the data usable.
Or we can check its function before loading the
data, today let's review Barbie's work by clicking.
In transforming data. On the left we see where Barbie
got the data from.
In the middle we see the real data on the
right, we can compare with testing the intelligent transformation work
he did for the trip.
We can edit and add them. At those
steps, for example, we see here that by way of
converting the front row.
In the column headers we also see that it changed
the data types.
It seems like everything makes
sense, so we don't need to change anything.
If we wanted to change something it would be as
simple as clicking on the buttons above.
Or would it be so advanced? How to update the
Code for every 1 of these steps?
The code, the code is called Ehmm Siri and is
a language of care and consultation that guarantees that each
step of the cri รณ consulta is based on
the previous one, so it is very easy to understand
the transformations that are made.
Now that we have the data and check out Barbie's
transformation work.
Let's move on to loading the data.
There are 3 icons on the left.
The first is called a
report, the next is called data, and the third is
called a model.
Now he's watching. A blank canvas where he will soon
be painting.
This is where data visualization happens.
We will return to this point later.
The next two are data and
model, and coincidentally we refer to what we do together,
such
as modeling from data. The data section is similar to
the transform data
section, except that where transforming data is for things that
will be done once in advance and will not be
updated until it is updated.
The entire dataset.
Data allows you to create measures that are emphasized in
real time as tailored.
That the report consumer filters the data.
It uses a piece of data called DAX.
Until it's more
advanced, don't worry about
this section, you'll know it's there.
The last section is the model that has the relationships
between the tables.
We can check the work of Power view and see
that the product connects the product table with the sales
table.
Each product in the product table corresponds to several products
in the product table.
Does that make sense? Good job for travel if I
wanted to do
something different, I would just have to double click
on it, on the line and make the updates.
Now, believe it or not, everything we've seen so far
is available in Microsoft Excel.
So what makes paying for trips so special?
These are two things. First is the ability to publish
all the data processing we've set up so far in
the cloud so that it can
be updated, updated, and shared. Second. It's the data visualization
capabilities.
What do they believe? Interconnected charts and graphs.
In a very intuitive way.
As an example I just click on the columns I
want and automatically create a table.
I click here and it becomes a bar chart.
You now have a complete overview of the fundamentals of
Pavia and I hope you liked the video.
Keep tuned in for more. We are going to move
very fast.